<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on John Lapeyre</title>
    <link>https://jlapeyre.github.io/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on John Lapeyre</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 02:13:21 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jlapeyre.github.io/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Broken links</title>
      <link>https://jlapeyre.github.io/news/brokenlinks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 14:41:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jlapeyre.github.io/news/brokenlinks/</guid>
      <description>Switching my site to a new website builder caused several external links to break, including search results linking to old content on the old site, for which internal links had been removed. So, I have been fixing this with aliases, but haven&amp;rsquo;t made all of them yet.
In the mean time, I see that google reacts much more quickly to a radical change in my site than it did 10 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JuliaCon 2018</title>
      <link>https://jlapeyre.github.io/news/juliacon2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 02:45:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jlapeyre.github.io/news/juliacon2018/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m excited to be giving a talk at JuliaCon 2018 on symbolic computation software in Julia.
I&amp;rsquo;m very curious to hear the perspective on Julia of the highly-distinguished, veteran, keynote speakers Sophie Wilson and Nicholas Higham. &amp;hellip; and excited (still) to meet all the brilliant Julia developers and users, &amp;hellip; and also about everything else that will be going on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New web site</title>
      <link>https://jlapeyre.github.io/news/newsite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 02:17:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jlapeyre.github.io/news/newsite/</guid>
      <description>I switched to a new website framework. Or rather, I began to use one. Till now, I had hand coded html/css borrowed from somewhere. But having managed content makes life easier, even for a simple site.
The previous content was a bit wooly from years of accretion and pruning. I more-or-less started fresh. But, I transferred some of the content to the new framework.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>