<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Music on John Lapeyre</title>
    <link>https://jlapeyre.github.io/music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Music on John Lapeyre</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 20:29:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jlapeyre.github.io/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Soul Intro to The Chicken</title>
      <link>https://jlapeyre.github.io/music/soul-intro-to-the-chicken-horn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2007 07:28:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jlapeyre.github.io/music/soul-intro-to-the-chicken-horn/</guid>
      <description>The most popular content on this website is &amp;ldquo;Distribution of entanglement in large-scale quantum networks&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip;. Nah, just kidding. By far the most popular is this transcription of the horn parts of the Soul Intro by Jaco Pastorius (or his band) to The Chicken by Pee Wee Ellis. I found a scan of a transcription by Mark Welcome. I re-typeset it and made a few corrections and additions. Here is a clip of Jaco and a band playing it in 1981.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Electric Lady Land (Instrumental)</title>
      <link>https://jlapeyre.github.io/music/study-of-instrumental-version-of-electric-lady-land/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2006 07:23:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jlapeyre.github.io/music/study-of-instrumental-version-of-electric-lady-land/</guid>
      <description>Electric Lady Land (Instrumental) Hendrix recorded a short, instrumental version of Electric Lady Land. Here is an mp3 of a recording I made while studying it. It would be a fun exercise to transcribe it, but that&amp;rsquo;s probably for another life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transcription of Marc Ribot&#39;s La Vida Es Un Sueño</title>
      <link>https://jlapeyre.github.io/music/transcription-of-la-vida-es-un-sueno/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2005 02:51:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jlapeyre.github.io/music/transcription-of-la-vida-es-un-sueno/</guid>
      <description>Transcription of Marc Ribot : La Vida Es Un Sueño Here is a transcription and recording I made of La Vida Es Un Sueño by Arsenio Rodriguez, arranged by Marc Ribot. The transcription is of the guitar (Ribot) and bass (Brad Jones) parts of the studio recording of the La Vida Es un Sueño. I did this transcription as an exercise to study Ribot&amp;rsquo;s playing. Here are the files for the transcription:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Notes to Transcription of Marc Ribot&#39;s Cover of La Vida es un Sueño</title>
      <link>https://jlapeyre.github.io/music/notes-on-transcription-of-la-vida-es-un-sueno/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2005 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jlapeyre.github.io/music/notes-on-transcription-of-la-vida-es-un-sueno/</guid>
      <description>Introduction These notes were made while transcribing 1 the studio recording of the guitar and bass parts of Marc Ribot&amp;rsquo;s cover of La Vida Es un Sueño. The transcription, recordings, etc. are here
Who is responsible for this music ? The original music and lyrics are by Arsenio Rodriguez, who wrote it in the early 1940&amp;rsquo;s. There is a good story, which may even be true, that says he arrived in New York from Cuba and the doctor told him that it was impossible to restore his eyesight, and shortly thereafter he dictated the song to his brother.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>